CARLOS OCEGUERA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JR

I am 40 years old and I am from the state of Sinaloa, Mexico. Since 2012, I have been working as a programming teacher. I worked for five years in the culinary field, but I decided to make a radical change in my life and study programming, which I consider my true passion. I am a self-taught person and I enjoy solving problems. I have a high tolerance for pressure, and I like things to be organized. I do not like taking shortcuts; I am always looking for ways to perfect things and procedures to make them more efficient.





CONTACT

Telephone: +52 695 108 4178

Mail: coceguerahegmail.com

Address: Fco. Camacho #80 Centro, Escuinapa, Sinaloa, México



Spanish Native

English 90%







PORTFOLIO

chefoce.github.io/Portfolio-CO/

GITHUB

github.com/chefoce/

LINKEDIN

www.linkedin.com/in/coceguerah



EDUCATION

Open and Distance University of Mexico

Software Development Engineering

Television Training Facility

Computer Systems Technician

Mexico's Culinary Institute

Bachelor's degree in Gastronomy, Culinary Arts



EXPERIENCE

Programming Teacher/ August 2012 - Present

- Subjects taught:
 - Java Object-Oriented Programming
 - Programming Techniques Management (C)
 - Databases (MySQL)
 - Web Development encompassing HTML, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript.

Freelance Developer / August 2018 - Present

 Development of websites, web applications with databases, social media management, and advertising campaigns for clients and small businesses.

Head Chef / 2010 - 2012

- Execute kitchen administrative duties.
- Recruit and oversee kitchen personnel.
- Handle input orders
- Manage product and personnel expenses.
- Organize and oversee culinary activities.



COURSES

- Responsive Web Design FreeCodeCamp
- Object-Oriented Programming on Java Open Intelligence